Guide to the Sam Kindrick Papers
The Wittliff Collections
Sam Kindrick Papers
1934-2018
1968-2018
The Wittliff Collections
Kindrick, Clarence Samuel, 1934-
SWWC.134
30 boxes
25 Linear Feet
The papers of reporter, photographer, and publisher, Sam Kindrick, span 1934-2018, and are arranged into three series: Photographs, Kindrick's Personal Papers, and Action Magazine. The bulk of the collection relates to Action Magazine, a monthly newspaper Kindrick launched in 1975. Included are approximately 4,000 photographs from the publication, and a near-complete run of the paper. Kindrick's personal papers include copies of his column from the San Antonio Express News, 1968-1974.
Scope and Contents
The papers of reporter and publisher, Sam Kindrick, span 1934-2018, and are arranged into three series: Photographs, Personal Papers, and Action Magazine Records. Photographs comprise the bulk of the collection and number approximately 4,000. Most are photographs of artists and musicians from Kindrick's Action Magazine files that document a veritable "who's who" of local and touring performers who played in San Antonio and the region from 1975 to the mid 2010s.
The photographs are arranged alphabetically, and notable artists and personalities include Asleep at the Wheel, Moe Bandy, Johnny Bush, Johnny Cash, Hondo Crouch, Joe Ely, Freddy Fender, Kinky Friedman, John Lee Hooker, Waylon Jennings & Jessie Colter, Steve Jordan, Augie Meyers, Willie Nelson, Johnny Rodriguez, Leon Russell, Doug Sahm, Billy Joe Shave, Jimmy Spacek, and Jerry Jeff Walker. The Willie Nelson photographs are substantial in number, and of note are some images of his father, Ira, as well as images of each of the band members.
The photographs also document the unique culture of 1970s-1980s Texas and include files on armadillos; artists & craftsmen; beer; chili cookoffs; and politicians. In addition, there are a number of photographs of sports personalities, pool players, boxers, and dare devils.
And finally, the photographs include some of Sam Kindrick's personal and family photos, including some from Kindrick's childhood, school days, and early reporting career. Images of Kindrick with performers are filed with the respective performer's file, such as Kinky Friedman, Augie Meyers, Willie Nelson, and Jerry Jeff Walker.
The bulk of Kindrick's personal papers include clippings of his "Offbeat" column that appeared in the San Antonio Express News, 1968-1974. The column is a precursor to the work he would later do at Action Magazine, and the subjects are similar: music, culture, off-beat stories of sports, politics, and society.
The final series relates to Action Magazine itself and includes some artist press releases, advertising files, some layout pages, a wire newspaper stand, and a near-complete run of the newspaper from 1975-2018.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Sam Kindrick, 2018
Biographical Notes
Clarence Samuel Kindrick (November 3, 1934 - ) is a Texas journalist, author and publisher. The longtime newspaper reporter and columnist is best known as the founder of Action Magazine in March 1975 and for his wild and wooly chronicling of the outlaw country music movement of the 1970s from his home base of San Antonio and Bulverde.
Kindrick was born in San Antonio and grew up in a religious household in Junction. He graduated from Junction High School in 1953 and graduated from Southwest Texas State University in 1957.
After short stints at the Bay City News and the Kerrville Daily Times, Kindrick joined the San Angelo Standard Times in 1958 as a general assignments reporter. In 1960, he was hired by the San Antonio Express-News where he worked as a reporter and columnist until 1975.
Kindrick forged close bonds with Willie Nelson, Clarence "Gatemouth" Brown, Kinky Friedman, Hondo Crouch and Jerry Jeff Walker, adopted their redneck rock attitude, look and partying ways. His outrageous gonzo style of reporting made him the Hunter S. Thompson of the emerging music scene.
Music -- Periodicals; Music -- Texas; Country music; Gonzo journalism; Kindrick, Clarence Samuel, 1934-
- Photographs, 1975-2018; 1975-2010
  Series Description
  The photographs are arranged alphabetically, and notable artists and personalities include Asleep at the Wheel, Moe Bandy, Johnny Bush, Johnny Cash, Hondo Crouch, Joe Ely, Freddy Fender, Kinky Friedman, John Lee Hooker, Waylon Jennings & Jessie Colter, Steve Jordan, Augie Meyers, Willie Nelson, Johnny Rodriguez, Leon Russell, Doug Sahm, Billy Joe Shave, Jimmy Spacek, and Jerry Jeff Walker. The Willie Nelson photographs are substantial in number, and of note are some images of his father, Ira, as well as images of each of the band members.The photographs also document the unique culture of 1970s-1980s Texas and include files on armadillos; artists & craftsmen; beer; chili cookoffs; and politicians. In addition, there are a number of photographs of sports personalities, pool players, boxers, and dare devils.And finally, the photographs include some of Sam Kindrick's personal and family photos, including some from Kindrick's childhood, school days, and early reporting career. Images of Kindrick with performers are filed with the respective performer's file, such as Kinky Friedman, Augie Meyers, Willie Nelson, and Jerry Jeff Walker.
  - Action Magazine Photographs, 1975-2018
    - Artists - A (28 photographs) including Keith Adams, Simmons Allison, Anacini (Lawrence Welk), Duke Anthony (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Action Magazine Employees (6 photographs, negatives, contact sheet) (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Alabama (2 photographs, press release) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Alan, Buddy (3 photographs, negatives) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Alexander, Susan [Legends of Texas Swing] (2 photographs) (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Amber Rose Trio (3 photographs) (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Amelia (12 photographs) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - American Peddlers (5 photographs) (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Anderson, John (1 photograph) (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Animals & Handlers (49 photographs) (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Armadillos (6 photographs, file re: armadillo logo & usage) (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Ashcroft, Steve (10 photographs); kickboxer (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Ashlock, Jessie (2 photographs); Cheatham Street, Bob Wills fiddler (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Asleep at the Wheel [1 of 2] (29 photographs) (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Asleep at the Wheel [2 of 2] (23 photographs, press releases) (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Austin City Limits Promotional Photographs (8 photographs) (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Ayala, Mike (2 photographs); boxer (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Ayala, Tony (22 photographs, newspaper clippings); boxer (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Artists - B [1 of 3] (54 photographs) including Bailey, Bill, Bailey, Razzy, Bobby Bland, Reverend Bill Joe Bob, The Boiz, Bob Bozman, Doyle Bramhall (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Artists - B [2 of 3] (67 photographs) including Backwoods Volunteers, Bad Boys, Barbosa, Black Cats, Blast 98, Joe Bob Burris (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Artists - B [3 of 3] (38 photographs) including Gatemouth Brown, Jim & Nessie Beal, Bett Butler, Marc Benno, Rick Broussard (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Bad Livers (8 photographs) (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Baker, Bobby (3 photographs) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Baker, Steven "Even Steven" (7 photographs, news clipping); motorcycle stunts (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Balcones Fault (9 photographs) (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Ball, Marcia (3 photographs) (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Bandera (3 photographs, press release) (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Bandy, Moe (28 photographs, press packet, negatives) (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Bare, Bobby (7 photographs, negatives) (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Barnett, Spot (3 photographs) (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Barton, Lou Ann (3 photographs) (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Beck, Edgar (6 photographs, negatives) rock craftsman (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Beely, Will (1 photograph, negatives) (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Beer – Ads, Executives, Employees (21 photographs) (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Beer – Lone Star (24 photographs, ads, contact sheets); Jerry Retzloff, Daryl Royal, Executives (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Behemoth (4 photographs) (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Bellson, Louie (5 photographs) (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Bergs Mill Symphony (2 photographs) (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Beresford (3 photographs) (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Billy Blues (5 photographs); restaurant (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Blackfoot (3 photographs) (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Black Oak Arkansas (4 photographs, press releases) (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Black Rose (2 photographs, press release) (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Blaker, Clay [Honky Tonk Band] (9 photographs, press packet) (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Bland, Bobby at Westwood Country Club, San Antonio (1 photograph) (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Bogus, Joe (7 photographs) (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Bone, Ponty (6 photographs) (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Bowman, Don (6 photographs) (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Broken Heart (5 photographs) (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Brooks, Lonnie (8 photographs) (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Brown, Clarence "Gatemouth" (7 photographs) (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Brown Hat Band (5 photographs, negatives) (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Brown, Jim Ed (3 photographs, press release) (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Buffett, Jimmy (1 photograph, Lone Star Beer promo) (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Burke, Frenchie (15 photographs, press release, negatives) (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Bush, Johnny (38 photographs, press release, negatives) including with Kindrick (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Artists - C (52 photographs) including Adam Carroll, Csi Csi Cisneros, Guy Clark, John Conlee, Earl Thomas Conley, Coyote Dreams (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Cactus Rose (4 photographs) (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Cain Sisters (8 photographs, negatives) (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Campi, Ray [Rockabilly Rebels] (1 photograph) (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Cangles, Ray (1 photograph, negatives) (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Canon, Carol (3 photographs) (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Caras, Jimmy (2 photographs, press release); pool player (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Carlson, Mel (4 photographs); woodworker (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Carrasco, Joe "King" (8 photographs, CD) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Carroll, Herb (4 photographs) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Carroll, Milton (3 photographs) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Casas, Jimmy (12 photographs) (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Cash, Johnny and June Carter (4 photographs) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Casual, Rick (4 photographs) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Cecil and Sylvia (6 photographs) (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Champion, Willie "El Curro" (8 photographs, negatives); incl. photos of dancers (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Cervero, Ramiro (2 photographs) (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Cheser, Greg [Little Bit of Texas] (2 photographs) (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Chylimpiad, San Marcos (19 photographs, press releases) incl. photos of armadillo races, beauty pageants, Jerry Retzloff, Ted Mondale (son of Vice President Walter Mondale), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Chylimpiad, 1983 (1 photograph, 2 rolls of negatives – damaged) (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Cypress (2 photographs) (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Cicchetti, Steve (5 photographs) (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Cisneros, Carol (6 photographs) (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Clark, Jubal (5 photographs) includes Ira Nelson (father of Willie Nelson) (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Climer, Glen [Climer's Rummage Barn] (5 photographs) (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Club Employees (57 photographs) (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Cobras (2 photographs) (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Coe, David Allen (10 photographs, 2 compact discs) (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Comedians & Actors: Marty Cohen (1), Jeff Dunham (1), Shirley Ann Hemphill (1), Bob Hope (1), Darrow Igus (1), Dan Johnson [The Flip Side of Flip] (6), Gabe Kaplan (1), Jimmie Walker (1) (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Conover, Tracy (3 photographs) (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Cooder Browne Band (20 photographs, clippings) (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cook-offs & Festivals (68 photographs) (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Cooper, Alice (2 photographs) (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Cooper, Dana (2 photographs, press packet) (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Cornelius, Helen (2 photographs) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Court, Jimmy (3 photographs) (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Cowan, Danny (4 photographs) (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Craftsmen & Artisans (47 photographs) includes Greg Choutes, Jonas Perkins, Bill Narum, tattoo artists, jewelry makers sculptors (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Crouch, Hondo (19 photographs) includes Kindrick, sculptor Jonas Perkins (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Crow, Alvin (6 photographs, clippings) (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Crowd Shots (16 photographs) (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Curry, Chris "Kid" (3 photographs) (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Cutrofello, Mary (3 photographs) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Artists - D (40 photographs) including The Denns, Bo Diddley, The Drifters (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Dale, Kenny (4 photographs) (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Daniels, Charlie (6 photographs, press release) (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Davis, Katherine Dawn (4 photographs) (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Day, Jimmy (7 photographs) (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Dead Crickets (6 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Dean, Jimmy (2 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Denim (2 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Dingler, John (2 photographs, press packet) (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Dino Lee (5 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dizzy Bloom (5 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Doctor Hook (3 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Dogtooth Violet (3 photographs, press release) (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Dominguez, Jay [Stoney Ridge] (12 photographs, press releases, negatives) (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Dorsey, Ben (3 photographs, 1 roll of negatives – damaged) (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Double Trouble [Stevie Ray Vaughan, Luanne Barton, Tommy Layton, Jackie Newhouse] (6 photographs), April 1979 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Douglas, Donna (2 photographs, contact sheet, negatives) (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Driver (3 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Drugstore Cowboys (27 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Drunks Against Mad Mothers [DAMM] (1 photograph, design material) (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Dugosh, Darryl (4 photographs, press packet) (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Dwyer, Dottsy Brodt (9 photographs, negatives), includes Roy Head (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Artists - E (12 photographs) including Randy Eichmann, Exotic Country (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - E-Nuff (4 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Earwood, Mundo (3 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Easy Money [Rusty Martin] (9 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Eckert, Bunny (3 photographs, negative) (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Edwards, Stony (8 photographs) includes Dottsy, Roy Head (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Ely, Joe (9 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Embs, Duke (3 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Emma Chaney Band (5 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Evil Mothers (4 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Extreme Heat (11 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Artists - F (33 photographs) including Sue Foley, Sara Fulcher, Keith Fuller (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - 501 Blues (4 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Fairchild, Barbara (12 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Felton, Gary (5 photographs) (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Fender, Freddy (8 photographs) including Augie Meyers (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Finlay, Kent (12 photographs, negatives) includes daughter Jenni Finlay, Cheatham Street Warehouse (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Flatt, Lester (4 photographs) only one photo is of Flatt (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Flip the Switch (4 photographs) (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Floore, John T. [and Stella] (2 photographs) (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Flores, Bobby (7 photographs) (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Flynt, Larry (3 photographs); press conference (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Food & Cooks (15 photographs) (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Foot Loose (4 photographs) (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Foster, Rex (14 photographs); jewelry (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Franklin, Larry (4 photographs, negatives, press packet) (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Friedman, Kinky [1 of 2] (35 photographs, photo CD with 34 images) (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Friedman, Kinky [2 of 2] (29 photographs, press release) including Sam Kindrick (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Fromholz, Steve (7 photographs, Lone Star Beer promo) (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Frugia, Bob (2 photographs) (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Artists - G (56 photographs) including Carroll Gilley, Mickey Gilley, Guido Gutierez, Pam Grimes (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Galvan, Joe and Jody (6 photographs); bootmaker (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Garibay, Randy (11 photographs, press release) includes Ernie & Randy Jr. (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Gatlin, Larry (2 photographs) (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Gibson, Susan (3 photographs) (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Gilbert, Esther (5 photographs, 1 slide) (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Gina, Lisa (16 slides) (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Gomez, Bobby (8 photographs) (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Greezy Wheels (5 photographs) (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Gruene Hall [Old Frank] (1 photograph) (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Artists - H (44 photographs) including Harrisons of Helter Skelter, Herman the German, Dan Hicks, Tommy Hill, Beverly Houston, Bugs Henderson (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Haggard, Merle (3 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Haines, Rainey (3 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Hale Gypsy (6 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Hall, Tom T. (2 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Halpin, Pat (4 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Hancock, Wayne "The Train" (4 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Happy Jazz Band (8 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Hargrove, Linda (5 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Harkins, Darrell (3 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Harris, Emmylou (4 photographs) w/ Bee Spears and Paul English (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Harvey, Alex (6 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Haynes, Alan (6 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Head, Roy (8 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Hearne, Bill & Bonnie (2 photographs, press packet) (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Hendrix, Terri (9 photographs), includes Lloyd Maines (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Hernandez, _____ (5 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Heyoka (5 photographs, press release) (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Hill, Eddie (3 photographs), speedboat (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Holiday, Ted & Birdie (2 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Hollywood Blues Band (6 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Holmes, John (4 photographs) adult film actor (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Holzhaus, Chris (17 photographs, negatives) (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Homefire (7 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Home Cookin' (4 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Honeysuckle Rose (4 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Hooker, Beth (3 photographs, contact sheet, negatives) (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Hooker, John Lee (3 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Houston, David (8 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Houston, Ron (8 photographs) (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Hubbard, Ray Wylie (30 photographs, press release, negatives) (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Artists I-J (33 photographs) including Illusion, Jokester, The Judds (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Jackson, Dale (2 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Jansky, Clifton and the Drifters (5 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Jay, Rodney (8 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Jenkins, Bob (18 photographs, 2 slides) (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Jennings, Waylon & Jessie Colter (9 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Johnny Dee and the Rocket 88s (8 photographs, negatives) (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Johnson, Angela (3 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Johnson, Snakeboy (5 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Joker Moon (6 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Jones, George (4 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Jones, Sammy (8 photographs, negatives); pool player (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Jones, Texarcola (3 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Jordan, Steve (9 photographs, clippings), includes son Steve Jordan II (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Jus' Country (8 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Artists - K (8 photographs) includes Paul Kandera, Ricky Keilman, Shelly King (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Kane, Candy (3 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Keen, Robert Earl, Jr. (5 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Kids, The (4 photographs, clipping) (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - King, Freddie (4 photographs, negative) (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - King, Jackie (6 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - King Peach Band (8 photographs, press release) (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - King, Shelley (8 photographs, CD) (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Kink, Sylvia (8 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Klocks (10 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Koehme, Phil (6 photographs, negatives) (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Kolb, Robert Lee (2 photographs, press release) (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Koock, Guch (9 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Krayolas (15 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Krezdorn, Rozanne (3 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - KSYM (3 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - K -Tels, [Erviesky] (6 photographs) (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Artists - L (51 photographs) including Ted Lacey, Danny Levinson, Lie, Lisa Lopez, Vic Lopez, Eric Lynn, Loretta Lynn, Rachel Laven, Rosie Ledet (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Larrys, The (5 photographs) (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Lee, Johnny (2 photographs) (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Lee, Robert (1 photograph, press packet) (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Leigh, Georgia (7 photographs) (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Lewis, Jerry Lee (4 photographs) (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Lewis, Steve [and the Legends] (4 photographs) (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Liberto, Ray (8 photographs) (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Linton, Guy & Evelyn (5 photographs) (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Little Bit of Texas, A (7 photographs, press release and calendar) (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Little Imo (3 photographs, press release) (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Little Joe y la Familia (3 photographs) (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Lopez, Victor (17 photographs) (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Lord, Mike (5 photographs, press releases, clippings) (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Los Lonely Boys (5 photographs) (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Lotions, The (3 photographs) (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Low Stony Ridge Mesquite (7 photographs); wood-workers (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Artists - M (1 of 2) (84 photographs) including Mata, Reba McEntire, Meister & Daniels, Art Mendoza, Montana Slim, Monty Montgomery (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Artists - M (45 photographs) including James McMurtry, Lloyd Maines, Houston Marchman, McKay Brothers (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Mac, Tiny (10 photographs) (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Mackey, Lorena (9 photographs, negatives) (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Mandrell, Barbara, Louse & Tina (4 photographs) (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Martinez, John David (4 photographs) (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Maximus (5 photographs) (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - McCall, Darrell (18 photographs, negatives) (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - McClinton, Delbert (2 photographs) (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - McFarland, Spanky (10 photographs, press releases) (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - McKenna, Danny (5 photographs) (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Media Personalities (44 photographs) (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Mendoza, Igo (13 photographs, press release, negatives); motorcycle stunt driver (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Messenger Band (4 photographs, negatives) (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Metheny Brothers (3 photographs) (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Meyers, Augie [1 of 2] (17 photographs, clippings, photo CD), includes Clay and Carol Meyers, Shawn Sahm (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Meyers, Augie [2 of 2] (51 photographs) includes Doug Sahm (2), Kindrick (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Milsap, Ronnie (4 photographs, press release) (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Minnesota Fats (5 photographs); pool player, includes Kindrick (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Mo Dels Band (5 photographs, negatives) (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Montgomery, Maggie (4 photographs) (Box 11, Folder 10)